{
  "modules": [
    {
      "moduleName": "Module 1: Basics",
      "topics": [
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 1: Greetings",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "你好",
              "pinyin": "nĭ hăo",
              "explanation": "Hello",
              "example": "你好，你叫什么名字?",
              "pinyinExample": "nǐ hǎo ， nǐ jiào shén me míng zì",
              "exampleTranslated": "Hello, what is your name?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "早安",
              "pinyin": "zǎo ān",
              "explanation": "Good Morning",
              "Example": "早安，起床了！",
              "PinyinExample": "zǎo ān ， qǐ chuáng liǎo",
              "exampleTranslated": "Good morning, it's time to wake up!"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "午安",
              "pinyin": "wǔ ān",
              "explanation": "Good Afternoon",
              "Example": "午安，你吃午饭了吗?",
              "PinyinExample": "wǔ ān ， nǐ chī wǔ fàn liǎo má",
              "exampleTranslated": "Good afternoon, have you eaten lunch?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "请问",
              "pinyin": "qǐng wèn",
              "explanation": "May I please ask, used at the start of the sentence",
              "Example": "请问厕所在哪?",
              "PinyinExample": "qǐng wèn cè suǒ zài nǎ",
              "exampleTranslated": "Excuse me, where is the toilet?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "谢谢",
              "pinyin": "xiè xiè",
              "explanation": "Thank you",
              "Example": "谢谢你帮我",
              "PinyinExample": "xiè xiè nǐ bāng wǒ",
              "exampleTranslated": "Thanks for helping me"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "_____, _____今天早餐吃什么？",
              "options": [
                "早安，谢谢",
                "午安，你好",
                "早安，请问",
                "晚安，请问"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "早安，请问",
              "explanation": "As the question is asking a question, we need to use 请问。早餐 means breakfast, therefore it would be logical for it to be in the morning, and the morning greeting would be 早安"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "我要睡觉了，_________",
              "options": ["早安", "午安", "谢谢", "晚安"],
              "correct_answer": "晚安",
              "explanation": "Question translates to I want to sleep already, hence the most fitting greeting would be 晚安"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "______ 你买午饭给我",
              "options": ["早安", "午安", "谢谢", "晚安"],
              "correct_answer": "谢谢",
              "explanation": "Question translates to thanking the person for buying lunch, hence the appropriate greeting would be thank you"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 2 Numbers",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "一二三一二三四五六七八九十四",
              "pinyin": "yī èr sān sì wǔ liù qī bā jiǔ shí",
              "explanation": "1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10",
              "Example": "我有三个苹果",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ yǒu sān gè píng guǒ",
              "exampleTranslated": "I have three apples"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "十一，十二，十三，二十",
              "pinyin": "shí yī, shí èr, shí sān, èr shí",
              "explanation": "Eleven, Twelve, Thirteen, Twenty",
              "Example": "我请了十五位朋友来我生日会",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ qǐng liǎo shí wǔ wèi péng yǒu lái wǒ shēng rì huì",
              "exampleTranslated": "I have invited 15 friends to my birthday party"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "一百，两百十二，五百二十三，九百九十九",
              "pinyin": "yī bǎi ， liǎng bǎi shí èr ， wǔ bǎi èr shí sān ， jiǔ bǎi jiǔ shí jiǔ",
              "explanation": "100, 212, 523, 999",
              "Example": "我刚刚捡到的钱包里有两百二十五块钱",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ gāng gāng jiǎn dào de qián bāo lǐ yǒu liǎng bǎi èr shí wǔ kuài qián",
              "exampleTranslated": "The wallet that I just picked up has 225 dollars inside."
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "一千，五千六百七十八， 一万两千三百四十五，六十七万八千九百零一",
              "pinyin": "yī qiān ， wǔ qiān liù bǎi qī shí bā ， yī wàn liǎng qiān sān bǎi sì shí wǔ ， liù shí qī wàn bā qiān jiǔ bǎi líng yī",
              "explanation": "1000, 12345, 678901",
              "Example": "您从中赚取的利息为二十三万四千五百六十七元",
              "PinyinExample": "nín cóng zhōng zhuàn qǔ de lì xī wéi èr shí sān wàn sì qiān wǔ bǎi liù shí qī yuán",
              "exampleTranslated": "You have earned $234,567 in interest"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "一百万，一亿",
              "pinyin": "yī bǎi wàn ， yī yì",
              "explanation": "One million, one billion",
              "Example": "本周末的彩票奖金是两百五十万",
              "PinyinExample": "běn zhōu mò de cǎi piào jiǎng jīn shì liǎng bǎi wǔ shí wàn",
              "exampleTranslated": "This weekend's lottery prize is $2.5 million"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "Translate 3,966 to chinese",
              "options": [
                "三十九百六十六",
                "三千九百六十六",
                "两千九百六十六",
                "三七六六"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "三千九百六十六",
              "explanation": "1: Does'nt make sense, 3: 2966, 4:3766"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "Translate 10,485 to chinese",
              "options": [
                "十千四百八十五",
                "十四百八十五",
                "一千四百八十五",
                "十四千八十五"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "十千四百八十五",
              "explanation": "2: 14085, 3: 1485, 4: 14085"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "Translate 6 million 50 thousand and 6 hundred to chinese",
              "options": [
                "六十亿五万零六百",
                "六百万零五万零六百",
                "六百五十六",
                "六百万五十千六十"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "六百万零五万零六百",
              "explanation": "1: 6 billion 50 thousand and 6 hundred, 3: 656, 4: 5 million, fifty thousand and sixty"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 3: Public Transport",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "地铁",
              "pinyin": "dì tiě",
              "explanation": "Mass Rapid Transit (MRT)",
              "example": "从文礼前往裕廊东，需乘坐三站地铁",
              "pinyinExample": "cóng wén lǐ qián wǎng yù láng dōng, xū chéng zuò sān zhàn dì tiě?",
              "exampleTranslated": "To travel from Boon Lay to Jurong East,take 3 stops on the MRT"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "巴士",
              "pinyin": "bā shì",
              "explanation": "Bus",
              "Example": "如果您想前往南洋理工大学，您需要从文礼巴士转换站乘坐179号巴士",
              "PinyinExample": "rú guǒ nín xiǎng qián wǎng nán yáng lǐ gōng dà xué ， nín xū yào cóng wén lǐ bā shì zhuǎn huàn zhàn chéng zuò 179 hào bā shì",
              "exampleTranslated": "Good morning, it's time to wake up!"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "德士",
              "pinyin": "dé shì",
              "explanation": "Taxi",
              "Example": "时间已经很晚了，您可能需要考虑乘坐德士返回住宿地点",
              "PinyinExample": "shí jiān yǐ jīng hěn wǎn le, nín kě yǐ kǎo lǜ chéng zuò dé shì fǎn huí zhù sù dì diǎn",
              "exampleTranslated": "It is getting late, you may want to consider taking a taxi back to your accommodation"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "飞机",
              "pinyin": "fēi jī",
              "explanation": "",
              "Example": "我们家人计划明年坐飞机去新加坡度假?",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ men jiā rén jì huà míng nián zuò fēi jī qù xīn jiā pō dù jià",
              "exampleTranslated": "Our family plans to take an airplane to Singapore for a vacation next year."
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "船",
              "pinyin": "chuán",
              "explanation": "Boat/Ferry",
              "Example": "那艘渡轮将乘客从新加坡港口送往印尼的巴淡岛。",
              "PinyinExample": "nà suǒ dù lún jiāng chéng kè cóng xīn jiāpō gǎng kǒu sòng wǎng Yìn ní de bā dàn dǎo",
              "exampleTranslated": "That ferry transports passengers from the Singapore port to Batam Island in Indonesia"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "新加坡河上有很多______，可以欣赏城市的美丽夜景",
              "options": ["飞机", "地铁", "船", "德士"],
              "correct_answer": "船",
              "explanation": "河 represent river, hence the only transport that could travel on water would be a boat/ferry,船 "
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "我需要乘坐 302 号________回家",
              "options": ["飞机", "地铁", "船", "巴士"],
              "correct_answer": "巴士",
              "explanation": "Question has prompted with a number, high chance would be bus"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "我下周乘________去香港",
              "options": ["飞机", "地铁", "船", "巴士"],
              "correct_answer": "飞机",
              "explanation": "Question has mentioned the author would be going to Hong Kong, therefore the highest probability would be a flight"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 4: Places of interest in Singapore",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "牛车水",
              "pinyin": "nĭ hăo",
              "explanation": "Chinatown",
              "example": "牛车水是新加坡的历史街区",
              "pinyinExample": "niú chē shuǐ shì xīn jiā pō de lì shǐ jiē qū",
              "exampleTranslated": "Chinatown is a historic district in Singapore?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "乌节路",
              "pinyin": "wū jié Lù",
              "explanation": "Orchard Road",
              "Example": "乌节路是新加坡著名的购物街道",
              "PinyinExample": "wū jié lù shì xīn jiā pō zhù míng de gòu wù jiē dào",
              "exampleTranslated": "Orchard Road is a famous shopping street in Singapore"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "滨海湾金沙",
              "pinyin": "bīn hǎi wān jīn shā",
              "explanation": "Marina Bay Sands",
              "Example": "滨海湾金沙是一个豪华度假胜地",
              "PinyinExample": "bīn hǎi wān jīn shā shì yī gè háo huá dù jià shèng dì",
              "exampleTranslated": "Marina Bay Sands is a luxury resort"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "纽顿熟食中心",
              "pinyin": "niú dùn shú shí zhōng xīn",
              "explanation": "Newton Food Centre",
              "Example": "纽顿熟食中心有各种美味的食物?",
              "PinyinExample": "niǔ dùn shú shí zhōng xīn yǒu gè zhǒng měi wèi de shí wù",
              "exampleTranslated": "Newton Food Center has a variety of delicious food"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "樟宜机场",
              "pinyin": "zhāng yí jī chǎng",
              "explanation": "Changi Airport",
              "Example": "樟宜机场是新加坡的主要国际机场",
              "PinyinExample": "Zhāng yí jī chǎng shì xīn jiā pō de zhǔ yào guó jì jī chǎng",
              "exampleTranslated": "Changi Airport is Singapore's main international airport"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "我们要去_______乘坐飞机去香港",
              "options": ["樟宜机场", "纽顿熟食中心", "滨海湾金沙", "乌节路"],
              "correct_answer": "樟宜机场",
              "explanation": "Question is stating that we are taking a flight, hence the only logical choice would be the airport"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "________ 有好多好吃的美食",
              "options": ["滨海湾金沙", "樟宜机场", "乌节路", "纽顿熟食中心"],
              "correct_answer": "纽顿熟食中心",
              "explanation": "The food centre would be the most fitting when talking about food"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "______ 你买午饭给我",
              "options": ["早安", "午安", "谢谢", "晚安"],
              "correct_answer": "谢谢",
              "explanation": "Question translates to thanking the person for buying lunch, hence the appropriate greeting would be thank you"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 5: Local Food",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "海南鸡饭",
              "pinyin": "nĭ hăo",
              "explanation": "Hello",
              "example": "海南鸡饭包括嫩滑的鸡肉、香味十足的鸡油饭和美味的辣椒酱",
              "pinyinExample": "nǐ hǎo ， nǐ jiào shén me míng zì",
              "exampleTranslated": "Hello, what is your name?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "榴莲",
              "pinyin": "zǎo ān",
              "explanation": "Good Morning",
              "Example": "榴莲是新加坡的国果",
              "PinyinExample": "zǎo ān ， qǐ chuáng liǎo",
              "exampleTranslated": "Good morning, it's time to wake up!"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "辣椒蟹",
              "pinyin": "wǔ ān",
              "explanation": "Good Afternoon",
              "Example": "午安，你吃午饭了吗?",
              "PinyinExample": "wǔ ān ， nǐ chī wǔ fàn liǎo má",
              "exampleTranslated": "Good afternoon, have you eaten lunch?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "沙爹",
              "pinyin": "qǐng wèn",
              "explanation": "May I please ask, used at the start of the sentence",
              "Example": "沙爹是一种美味的烤肉串，通常搭配花生酱?",
              "PinyinExample": "shā diē shì yī zhǒng měi wèi de kǎo ròu chuàn, tōng cháng dā pèi huā shēng jiàng.",
              "exampleTranslated": "Excuse me, where is the toilet?"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 0,
              "word": "咖椰吐司",
              "pinyin": "xiè xiè",
              "explanation": "Thank you",
              "Example": "咖椰吐司的脆皮和柔软内馅相得益彰",
              "PinyinExample": "kā yē tǔ sī de cuì pí hé róu ruǎn nèi xiàn xiāng dé yì zhāng",
              "exampleTranslated": "Thanks for helping me"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "_____, _____今天早餐吃什么？",
              "options": [
                "早安，谢谢",
                "午安，你好",
                "早安，请问",
                "晚安，请问"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "早安，请问",
              "explanation": "As the question is asking a question, we need to use 请问。早餐 means breakfast, therefore it would be logical for it to be in the morning, and the morning greeting would be 早安"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "我要睡觉了，_________",
              "options": ["早安", "午安", "谢谢", "晚安"],
              "correct_answer": "晚安",
              "explanation": "Question translates to I want to sleep already, hence the most fitting greeting would be 晚安"
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "______ 你买午饭给我",
              "options": ["早安", "午安", "谢谢", "晚安"],
              "correct_answer": "谢谢",
              "explanation": "Question translates to thanking the person for buying lunch, hence the appropriate greeting would be thank you"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 6: Review",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "",
              "options": ["", "", "", ""],
              "correct_answer": "",
              "explanation": ""
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "",
              "options": ["", "", "", ""],
              "correct_answer": "",
              "explanation": ""
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "",
              "options": ["", "", "", ""],
              "correct_answer": "",
              "explanation": ""
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "",
              "options": ["", "", "", ""],
              "correct_answer": "",
              "explanation": ""
            },
            {
              "gameFormat": 1,
              "question": "",
              "options": ["", "", "", ""],
              "correct_answer": "",
              "explanation": ""
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },

    {
      "moduleName": "Module 2: Easy",
      "topics": [
        {
          "topicName": "xxx"
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 2: Weather",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "气温",
              "pinyin": "qì wēn",
              "explanation": "temperature",
              "Example": "今天的气温很热",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān de qì wēn hěn rè",
              "exampleTranslated": "Today's temperature is very hot"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "多云",
              "pinyin": "duō yún",
              "Explaination": "cloudy",
              "Example": "今天的天空多云",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān de tiān kōng duō yún",
              "exampleTranslated": "The sky looks cloudy today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "下雨",
              "pinyin": "xià yǔ",
              "Explaination": "raining",
              "Example": "目前正在下雨",
              "PinyinExample": "mù qián zhèng zài xià yǔ",
              "exampleTranslated": "It is currently raining"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "雷雨",
              "pinyin": "léi yǔ",
              "Explaination": "thunderstorm",
              "Example": "天气预报预计有雷雨",
              "PinyinExample": "tiān qì yù bào yù jì yǒu léi yǔ",
              "exampleTranslated": "The weather forecast predicts a thunderstorm"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "下雪",
              "pinyin": "xià xuě",
              "Explaination": "snow",
              "Example": "新加坡不下雪",
              "PinyinExample": "xīn jiā pō bù xià xuě",
              "exampleTranslated": "It does not snow in Singapore"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What does “今天的天气很热” mean?",
              "options": [
                "Today’s weather is very cold",
                "Today’s weather is very windy",
                "Today’s weather is very hot",
                "Today’s weather is very snowy"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "Today’s weather is very hot",
              "explanation": "热 means hot"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "How do you say Cloudy in Chinese?",
              "options": ["多云", "雾天", "冰雹", "寒冷"],
              "correct_answer": "多云",
              "explanation": "多云 means cloudy"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What does “下雨” mean?",
              "options": ["Raining", "Snowing", "Sunny", "Windy"],
              "correct_answer": "Raining",
              "explanation": "下雨 means raining"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 3: Directions",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "东",
              "pinyin": "dōng",
              "Explaination": "east",
              "Example": "太阳从东方升起",
              "PinyinExample": "tài yáng cóng dōng fāng shēng qǐ",
              "exampleTranslated": "The sun rises from the east"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "西",
              "pinyin": "xī",
              "Explaination": "west",
              "Example": "太阳在西方落下",
              "PinyinExample": "tài yáng zài xī fāng luò xià",
              "exampleTranslated": "The sun sets in the west"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "左",
              "pinyin": "zuǒ",
              "Explaination": "left",
              "Example": "他叫我左转",
              "PinyinExample": "tā jiào wǒ zuǒ zhuǎn",
              "exampleTranslated": "He told me to turn left"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "直走",
              "pinyin": "zhí zǒu",
              "Explaination": "straight ahead",
              "Example": "如果我直走我就会到达商店",
              "PinyinExample": "rú guǒ wǒ zhí zǒu wǒ jiù huì dào dá shāng diàn",
              "exampleTranslated": "I will reach the store if I walk straight"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "上楼",
              "pinyin": "shàng lóu",
              "Explaination": "go upstairs",
              "Example": "她上楼去找妈妈",
              "PinyinExample": "tā shàng lóu qù zhǎo mā mā",
              "exampleTranslated": "She went upstairs to look for mother"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What does “我后退一步，然后向左转” mean?",
              "options": [
                "I stepped back, then turned right",
                "I stepped forwards, then turned left",
                "I stepped back, then turned left",
                "I stepped forwards, then turned right"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "I stepped back, then turned left",
              "explanation": "后退 means stepped back, 左转 means turn left"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What is the Chinese translation for North?",
              "options": ["东", "南", "西", "北"],
              "correct_answer": "北",
              "explanation": "北 means north"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "How would you say Go Upstairs in Chinese?",
              "options": ["下楼", "上楼", "出门", "停车"],
              "correct_answer": "上楼",
              "explanation": "上楼 means go upstairs"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 4: Sights and Sounds at the Market",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "顾客",
              "pinyin": "gù kè",
              "Explaination": "customer",
              "Example": "她正忙着为顾客服务",
              "PinyinExample": "tā zhèng máng zhuó wéi gù kè fú wù",
              "exampleTranslated": "She is busy serving the customer"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "鱼",
              "pinyin": "yú",
              "Explaination": "fish",
              "Example": "爸爸说今天市场上的鱼很新鲜",
              "PinyinExample": "bà bà shuō jīn tiān shì cháng shàng de yú hěn xīn xiān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad says the fish at the market today was very fresh"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "购物篮",
              "pinyin": "gòu wù lán",
              "Explaination": "shopping cart",
              "Example": "我们推着购物篮在市场里转悠",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ mén tuī zhuó gòu wù lán zài shì cháng lǐ zhuǎn yōu",
              "exampleTranslated": "We pushed the shopping cart around the market"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "收银台",
              "pinyin": "shōu yín tái",
              "Explaination": "checkout",
              "Example": "我们去收银台付钱",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ mén qù shōu yín tái fù qián",
              "exampleTranslated": "We went to the checkout area to pay"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "巴刹",
              "pinyin": "bā chà",
              "Explaination": "market",
              "Example": "今天我去了巴刹",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān wǒ qù liǎo bā chà",
              "exampleTranslated": "Today I went to the market"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "How do you say Customer in Chinese?",
              "options": ["顾客", "购物篮", "收银台", "收据"],
              "correct_answer": "顾客",
              "explanation": "顾客 means customer"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What is the Chinese translation for Shopping cart?",
              "options": ["收银台", "收据", "货架", "购物篮"],
              "correct_answer": "购物篮",
              "explanation": "购物篮 means shopping cart"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "Translate “我买了一些鱼”",
              "options": [
                "I bought some eggs",
                "I bought some vegetables",
                "I bought some fish",
                "I bought some meat"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "I bought some fish",
              "explanation": "鱼 means fish"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 5: Cooking",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "刀",
              "pinyin": "dāo",
              "Explaination": "knife",
              "Example": "妈妈用刀切鸡肉",
              "PinyinExample": "mā mā yòng dāo qiē jī ròu",
              "exampleTranslated": "Mum uses a knife to cut chicken"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "煮",
              "pinyin": "zhǔ",
              "Explaination": "cook",
              "Example": "爷爷正在煮菜",
              "PinyinExample": "yé yé zhèng zài zhǔ cài",
              "exampleTranslated": "Grandpa is cooking dishes"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "筷子",
              "pinyin": "kuài zǐ",
              "Explaination": "chopsticks",
              "Example": "我用筷子夹食物",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ yòng kuài zǐ jiā shí wù",
              "exampleTranslated": "I use chopsticks to grab my food"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "炸",
              "pinyin": "zhà",
              "Explaination": "fry",
              "Example": "我喜欢吃炸鸡",
              "PinyinExample": "wǒ xǐ huān chī zhà jī",
              "exampleTranslated": "I like to eat fried chicken"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "晚餐",
              "pinyin": "wǎn cān",
              "Explaination": "dinner",
              "Example": "今天爸爸带我们出去吃晚餐",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What does “妈妈正在煮晚餐” mean?",
              "options": [
                "Father is cooking lunch",
                "Mother is cooking breakfast",
                "Mother is cooking dinner",
                "Father is cooking breakfast"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "Mother is cooking dinner",
              "explanation": "晚餐 means dinner"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What does “筷子” mean?",
              "options": ["Chopsticks", "Spoon", "Fork", "Knife"],
              "correct_answer": "Chopsticks",
              "explanation": "筷子 means chopsticks"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What is the Chinese translation for Knife?",
              "options": ["碗", "刀", "筷子", "炉子"],
              "correct_answer": "刀",
              "explanation": "刀 means knife"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 6: Review",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "Translate “妈妈叫我去巴刹买菜”",
              "options": [
                "Mother told me to go to the market to buy groceries",
                "Mother told me to go to school to study",
                "Mother told me to go to the clinic to buy medicine",
                "Mother told me to go to the hawker center to buy food "
              ],
              "correct_answer": "Mother told me to go to the market to buy groceries",
              "explanation": "巴刹 means market"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "What is “It looks like it is about to rain.” in Chinese?",
              "options": [
                "天气看起来要下雪了",
                "天气看起来要下雨了",
                "今天的天气很热",
                "今天的天气很凉"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "天气看起来要下雨了",
              "explanation": "下雨 means rain"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "How would you say “the market is four bus stops away” in Chinese?",
              "options": [
                "距离巴刹有一个公交车站",
                "距离巴刹有两个公交车站",
                "距离巴刹有四个公交车站",
                "距离巴刹有三个公交车站"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "距离巴刹有四个公交车站",
              "explanation": "四 is four"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "Translate “我买了两条鱼和一只鸡”",
              "options": [
                "I bought two fishes and three chickens",
                "I bought two fishes and one chicken",
                "I bought three fishes and one chicken",
                "I bought one fish and two chickens"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "I bought two fishes and one chicken",
              "explanation": "两条鱼 means two fishes, 一只鸡 means one chicken"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 1,
              "question": "Translate “今天奶奶给我们做了晚餐”",
              "options": [
                "Grandma is making lunch today",
                "Grandma is making breakfast today",
                "Grandma is making supper today",
                "Grandma is making dinner today"
              ],
              "correct_answer": "Grandma is making dinner today",
              "explanation": "晚餐 means dinner"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "moduleName": "Module 3: Intermediate",
      "topics": [
        {
          "topicName": "Topic 1: Family Greetings",
          "questions": [
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "爸爸，妈妈",
              "pinyin": "wǎn cān",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "弟弟，妹妹，哥哥，姐姐",
              "pinyin": "Younger brother, younger sister, Older brother, older sister",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "爷爷，奶奶",
              "pinyin": "Paternal Grandfather, paternal grandmother",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "外公，外婆",
              "pinyin": "Paternal Grandfather, paternal grandmother",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "外公，外婆",
              "pinyin": "Paternal Grandfather, paternal grandmother",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "伯伯，叔叔，姑姑，姑妈",
              "pinyin": "Paternal Grandfather, paternal grandmother",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            },
            {
              "gameformat": 0,
              "word": "阿姨，舅舅，姨妈",
              "pinyin": "Paternal Grandfather, paternal grandmother",
              "Explaination": "Father, Mother",
              "Example": "今天，爸爸和妈妈没做工",
              "PinyinExample": "jīn tiān bà bà dài wǒ mén chū qù chī wǎn cān",
              "exampleTranslated": "Dad is bringing us out for dinner today"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "topicName": "xxx",
          "questions": []
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
